[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These biological poisons damage bio systems on contact. The injuries they cause resemble burns.", "correct_answer": "Corrosives", "incorrect_answers": ["Oxidizers", "Halides", "Neurotoxins"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Renee Soutendijk played Eve and her creator in the movie Eve of Destruction. In which country was Renee born?", "correct_answer": "The Netherlands", "incorrect_answers": ["Canada", "Turkey", "France"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements about the Australian fauna is true?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Australia is the only continent that has more venomous than non-venomous snake species", "Two of the five known species of monotremes live in Australia", "Placental mammals are relatively rare in Australia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was the Skylon Tower, Niagaras most famous landmark, built?", "correct_answer": "in the 1960s", "incorrect_answers": ["in the 1950s", "in the 1940s", "in the 1990s"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A potato will sometimes have green skin. What is characteristic of this skin?", "correct_answer": "It contains a poisonous alkaloid.", "incorrect_answers": ["It is sweet.", "It identifies a foreign (non USA) potato.", "It is ugly but edible."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Absinthe was most popular in this country as it was the common beverage among artists and writers in the late 19th and early 20th centuries.", "correct_answer": "France", "incorrect_answers": ["Germany", "Italy", "England"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "More than half of the Yukon River is located within this American state.", "correct_answer": "Alaska", "incorrect_answers": ["North Dakota", "Kansas", "Texas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first spacecraft to study the planet Mercury?", "correct_answer": "Mariner 10", "incorrect_answers": ["Voyager 2", "Mariner 11", "Mariner 9"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1980 movie won the Academy Award for Best Picture at the 53rd Academy Awards in 1981?", "correct_answer": "Ordinary People", "incorrect_answers": ["Raging Bull", "The Elephant Man", "Coal Miners Daughter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Hyenas are most closely related to what creatures?", "correct_answer": "Mongoose", "incorrect_answers": ["Badger", "Bears", "Cats"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In blocking domino games when does the scoring of the game happen?", "correct_answer": "At the end of the game", "incorrect_answers": ["At the beginning of the game", "In the middle of the game", "Throughout the entire game"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2002, this actor was nominated by The Academy for the 12th time, thus becoming the male actor with the most Oscar nominations.", "correct_answer": "Jack Nicholson", "incorrect_answers": ["Tom Hanks", "Sir Laurence Olivier", "Matt Damon"]}]